https://www.kansys.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
In this Privacy Policy (“statement”), we, Kansys Inc, provide
information about how we collect, use, disclose, and transfer personal
information from you, an individual person and website visitor, through Kansys’
publicly accessible websites.
Protecting consumer privacy is important to the Company and Kansys
complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S. Privacy
Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the
collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the
European Union and Switzerland to the United States. Kansys has certified to
the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If
there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy
Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more
about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please
visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/. Kansys commitments under the Privacy Shield
are subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the United States
Federal Trade Commission.
This statement outlines our general policy and practices for
implementing the Principles, including the types of information we gather, how
we use it and the notice and choice affected individuals have regarding our use
of and their ability to correct that information.
This statement applies to all personal information collected or
received by the Company through our website and the Kansys billing platform(s).
Collected Data & Data Usage:
The Kansys billing system’s collect information under the direction of our
Clients and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data
it processes. If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer
like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact
the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal
information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to
subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our
Clients.
An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend,
or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Client (the data
controller). If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.
We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients
for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. We will retain this
personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve
disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Privacy Shield
Kansys complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and Swiss-U.S.
Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce
regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information
transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States.
Kansys has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the
Privacy Shield Principles.  If there is any conflict between the terms in
this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield
Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Privacy Shield program,
and to view our certification, please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/
Kansys is subject to investigatory and enforcement powers of the
U.S. Federal Trade Commission.
Users may have the option to select binding arbitration under
the Privacy Shield Panel for the resolution of your complaint under certain
circumstances. For further information, please see the Privacy Shield website
to learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework at https://www.privacyshield.gov.
Cookies:
When you interact with the Kansys website or software service, we may use
cookies to help make your experiences easy and meaningful. “Cookies” are a
technology employed by many other websites and are small data files stored on
your computer. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to
your computer.
Standing alone, cookies do not identify you personally. They merely
recognize your browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to Kansys,
either by responding to a promotional offer, completing a contact or interest
form or registering for an account, you remain anonymous to Kansys.
Third-Party Sites:
Our websites may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of
interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you
should note that we do not have any control over the linked website. Therefore,
we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information
which you provide while visiting such sites.
Such sites are not governed by this privacy statement and may or
may not be compliant with privacy laws. You should exercise caution and look at
the privacy statement, if available, of the website in question.
Sharing of Collected Data:
Kansys does not share any collected information with 3rd party
entities.
Correcting & Updating Data:
Kansys is dedicated to maintaining accurate and up to date Customer Data.
If you need to update Data and/or billing information or to have your
information deleted please email support@Kansysholdings.com or call 913-971-1700.
Kansys will respond to your correction or update request within 30 days from
the date of your request.
Security & Breach Notification:
Kansys has placed commercially reasonable security measures in place to protect
the integrity, availability, and confidentiality of Data. These measures include
policies, procedures, employee training, and physical access and logical
security controls. In addition, when accessing the Kansys software systems,
Data transmitted to Kansys’ servers are secured using standard security
protocols and mechanisms such as SSL encryption to ensure data confidentiality
and integrity.
If individual personal Data is acquired, or is reasonably
believed to have been acquired, by an unauthorized person and applicable law
requires notification of affected individuals, Kansys will issue a notification
of the breach by email or fax or, if Kansys is unable to contact the individual
by these means, then by U.S. mail. Notice will also be sent to Customers when a
breach affects Customer-provided Data, and to legal and law enforcement
authorities as required under current laws and regulations. Any measures
necessary for Kansys or legal and law enforcement to determine the scope of the
breach and to assure or restore the integrity of the data system will be taken.
Kansys may delay notification to Customers and/or individuals if Kansys or a
law enforcement agency determines that the notification will impede a criminal
investigation, unless and until Kansys or the agency determines that
notification no longer compromises an investigation.
Controlling your personal information on our websites
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal
information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time
by writing to us at, Kansys, 910 W Frontier Lane, Olathe KS,  66061 or emailing us at info@Kansys.com
You may request details of personal information which we hold
about you under the Data Protection Act, 1998. If you would like a copy of the
information held on you, please write to the address above. A small fee may be
payable.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is
incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, using
the contact information provided above. We will promptly correct any
information found to be incorrect.
Data Integrity:
We only process Personal Information in a way that is compatible with and
relevant for the purpose for which it was collected or authorized by our
clients. To the extent necessary for those purposes, we take measures to ensure
that Personal Information is accurate, complete, current and reliable for its
intended use.
See the section above regarding “Controlling your personal
information” for details on how to restrict or obtain a copy or correct your
personal information we may hold.
Enforcement:
We use a self-assessment approach to assure compliance with this statement and
periodically verify that the policy is accurate, comprehensive for the
information intended to be covered, prominently displayed, completely
implemented and accessible and in conformity with the Principles. In compliance
with the Privacy Shield Principles, Kansys commits to resolve complaints about
our collection or use of your personal information. EU and Swiss individuals
with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first
contact Kansys via mail at:
Kansys, 910 W Frontier Lane, Olathe, KS  66061 Attn: Data Privacy
Kansys has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield
complaints to JAMS, an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the
United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint
from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction,
please contact or visit www.jamsadr.com for more information or to file a
complaint. The services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you. If neither Kansys
nor our dispute resolution provider resolves your complaint, you may have the
possibility to engage in binding arbitration through the Privacy Shield Panel.Policy Updates:
Kansys reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy and notify users of any
changes by posting a prominent notice on the privacy section of our website.
READY TO GET STARTED? CALL US AT 1-800-981-6491 OR
REQUEST MORE INFO
Our Mission
We strive to be the most trusted solutions provider across our areas of expertise. We approach each engagement by determining how we can add maximum value to our client’s environment and business goals by leveraging our extensive library of solutions to best reach the desired outcomes.
Software
|Products|
The Kansys Edge
KCFE
|Built For|
Financial Exchanges
Telecom Billing Software
Transportation
